(Raj:)During which she defected
to North Korea.
(Howard:)Two booty calls with Leslie Winkle.
(Raj:)For which she awarded him the nickname
Speed-of-Light Leonard.
And a three-hour dinner with Penny.
Which would've been two and a half if they
ordered the soufflé when they sat down.
(Howard:)Based on the geometric progression...
(Howard:)...his relationship with Stephanie
should have ended after 20 minutes.
(Sheldon:)Yes, I'm aware of the math.
(Sheldon:)Y equals 27 days over 12 to the nth.
(Sheldon:)The issue remains.
(Sheldon:)How do we circumvent
his inevitable rejection?
(Raj:)Well, if you want to guarantee his appeal
to Stephanie...
(Raj:)...your best bet would be
to kill all the other men on the planet.
(Howard:)I'll tell you what you shouldn't do.
That body spray...
(Howard:)...where the women undress
when they smell it?
(Howard:)That doesn't work at all.
(Howard:)No matter how much you put on.
(Sheldon:)So that's all you've got? Apocalyptic
genocide and "Go easy on the cologne"?
- Yes.
- Yeah.